quanticapps.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy – QuanticApps

It’s very simple, we don’t collect any personal information from you. We use third-party SDKs and they might collect information such as location, device id to improve the service they are providing within the apps. Please find below their respective policies. 

We will collect technical information that may also be personal data (e.g. IP-address, device ID number etc.) from your device in order for us to be able to provide the functionality of the Application. This collected information is required for us and for our sub-suppliers to verify that your device is accurately registered. We reserve the right to use such information for statistics and user support.

Further, we will access and process information on your specific use of the Application, your location, device information, contact lists, interactions with other elements in the Application, Google Advertising ID (AAID), Apple Identifier for Advertising (IDFA). Some services that are part of the Application may require a specific consent from you. Where a specific consent is required, we will let you know and ask you to provide us herewith. 

THE THIRD PARTY SDKs AND THEIR RESPECTIVE PRIVACY POLICY We use 2 different SDKs in almost all our apps, they are listed below: 

Admob: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=GB  
Batch: https://batch.com/privacy-policy  
Firebase: https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics   
Fabric: https://fabric.io/privacy 

It’s very simple again, we don’t store any information from you on our servers. 

Users can opt-out of all information collection by removing the app from the device. Users have the right to ask the third party SDK (contact email in their policies) not to continue the processing of personal data. Users can exercise their rights to prevent processing by contacting them using their email.
